wazeefa1.com 2010-10-14

# Kuwait Jobs, Jobs in Kuwait, Gulf, Middle East, Dubai, Saudi Arabia

|   
---  
|  | Home |  |  Advertise with us |  |  Search Jobs |  | E-mail marketing solutions |  | Browse Companies |  | Contact Us |   
---|---|---|---|---|---|---|---|---|---|---|---|---  
  |   
|  |  | 

|   
---  
  
| View Thousands of   
**fresh** registered CV’s  

  |   
  
|   Privacy Policy  
---  

**Privacy Policy**

Wezeefa1 is strongly committed to the confidentiality of your job search and privacy of information on your resume and/or any other information you may submit. This privacy statement demonstrates wazeefa1 commitment to privacy. As a result of business changes, wazeefa1 may be required on occasion to make changes to its privacy policy. Reasonable efforts will be used to publish any changes.   
Your resume, and any other personal data, is not resold in any manner. If you are responding to a job posting or in any other way communicating information to wazeefa1, it can be shared from time to time with a third party at the sole discretion of wazeefa1  
This is to provide you with more effective job search services, as Web site recruiting is just one avenue of our recruiting efforts. We will use our best efforts to ensure that the information you submit to us remains private. However, wazeefa1 does not assume responsibility or liability for any actions of independent third parties.  
Wazeefa1, reserves the right to monitor and disclose to government officials or law enforcement, without your consent, any communications and personally identifiable information whenever prompted to do so by legal authorities, even when you have requested that your information not be disclosed to third parties.  
You should be aware of risks when you communicate online via e-mail. Personal information may be collected and used by others outside of wazeefa1, to send you unsolicited e-mails or postal mailings. Wazeefa1 has no control over these actions. Only wazeefa1, employees have first-line access to your personal data, and they are fully aware of our privacy policy and committed to it.  
If you are responding or applying to a job posted on this Web site, or in any other way communicating personal data, you are confirming your agreement to this privacy policy.  
  
  |
